# NICOLAS CÉSAIRE

#### **PORTFOLIO**

new-portfolio-alpha-snowy-59.vercel.app

10-5850, Chambord Street Montréal, Québec H2G 3B6

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm searching for a job that will allow me to utilize my years of experience in the administrative field, while teaching me new skills simultaneously. My versatility, attention to detail and inquisitive nature make me an asset to any team I work with.

## PROFESSIONAL QUALITIES

- Self-confident
- Organised
- Reliable
- Goal oriented

#### **LANGUAGES**

- French Spoken and written
- English Spoken and written

#### **SOFTWARE**

- Windows
- Word
- PowerPoint
- Excel
- Outlook
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Git
- C++,
- Java et C#
- Node.JS

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Banque TD POS troubleshooting and support	2018 to this day
<b>Desjardins</b> Customer service, technical support and sales	2017 – 2018
<b>Telus Mobility</b> Customer service, technical support and sales	2014 – 2017
Fossil Canada Sales of vintage inspired accessories	2012 – 2014
Aldo Shoes Sales of shoes and fashion accessories	2012 – 2012
Bureau des interviewers professionnels (BIP) Over the phone surveys (English/French)	2010 – 2012
<b>TLP Transport</b> Handling crates of different sizes Gather orders with a pallet truck	2009
ASPAT – Association de soccer de Pointe-aux-Trembles Soccer referee	2007 – 2008

## **EDUCATION**

Concordia Bootcamp Full Stack Web Development	2023
Codecademy Web developer (HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, SQL, Git) C++, Swift	2019
Collège de Rosemont Social Sciences	2009 - 2011
École secondaire Pointe-aux-Trembles SSD – Secondary School Diploma	2004 – 2009